ALEXIS QUINTUÑA

alexisiquintuna@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/alexis-quintuna | github.com/alexisquintuna | alexisquintuna.com

Creative web developer with a passion for turning design into captivating digital experiences using cutting-edge tools. Known for blending technical precision with visual storytelling to build interactive, performance-driven websites that stand out.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Object-Oriented Programming: .Net | JavaScript

Web Application Development: HTML | CSS | ASP.NET Core | Vue.js | React | Node.js | Express | TailWind

Database Programming: ADO.NET | Table Design | E/R diagrams | MVC | MongoDB

Development Tool & Techniques: Agile | Unit Testing | Figma | Postman | WebFlow | SquareSpace | Wordpress | WIX | Adobe

After Effects | Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Illustrator

EDUCATION

Tech Elevator, Columbus, OH

SEPT 2022 - DEC 2022

Attended a 14-week full-stack coding boot camp learning how to create dynamic web-based software systems using .NET/C# providing 800+ hours of development education and application.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Studio8E8, New Albany, OH

OCT 2023 - PRESENT

Creative Developer

- Evolved from Web Developer to Creative Developer within 3 months by consistently pushing the boundaries of design implementation, blending code and visual storytelling to craft immersive digital experiences.
- Brought designs to life using advanced web animation and interaction tools such as GSAP, Three.js, WebGL, and Adobe After Effects—transforming static mockups into rich, fluid, and responsive user experiences.
- Trusted with leadership responsibilities on high-impact projects, often stepping into a creative lead role in the absence of seniority, thanks to a strong design-to-dev intuition and technical execution.

Astra Studio, Columbus, OH

January 2023 – October 2023

Contract Web Developer

- Enhanced the team by quickly learning the company's workflow and procedures, sharing new perspectives and ideas, and helping the team find innovative solutions
- Secured, executed, and completed two projects on time and within budget, receiving positive feedback from clients and co-workers, working closely with clients to gather requirements and deliver a product that met their needs
- Demonstrated the ability to handle multiple projects simultaneously and think quickly on my feet, successfully resolving unexpected challenges, adapting to changing circumstances, and prioritizing tasks
- Devoted to learning new tools and technologies, such as WordPress, Squarespace, and Wix, to grow the company's clientele, increasing the company's clientele by 3x, an estimated value of over \$50,000 annually

OfRoot, Columbus, OH

March 2021 - August 2021

Web Developer Intern

- Gained experience in all aspects of web development, from writing and designing web page content to developing and maintaining websites, using authoring and scripting languages to create interactive and dynamic websites
- Demonstrated strong problem-solving and analytical skills by developing detailed test plans that ensured that websites were tested thoroughly.
- Worked independently and as part of a team to deliver projects on time, collaborating with team members to share ideas and solve problems.

The Roosevelt Coffeehouse, Columbus, OH

September 2019 - October 2023

Lead Barista

 Operated a coffee shop with a proven track record of success, generating over \$3000 in daily sales and consistently receiving positive feedback.

- Demonstrated ability to juggle multiple projects and roles effectively, adapting to the company's needs and being a team player
- Took ownership of new different requests, identified growth opportunities, and increased sales by 15%